https://filmmonterey.org/terms/

Terms & Conditions
Please read the following terms and conditions carefully as it sets out the terms of a legally binding agreement between you (the visitor) and the Monterey County Film Commission.
Privacy Policy
The Monterey County Film Commission is dedicated to protecting your privacy as you use our web site. Our policy is that no personal information will be collected about you unless you choose to provide it, and that any personal information which you provide us will be safeguarded and not shared with others for any reason.
If during your visit to our site you only browse, read pages or download material, we can not collect any information that will identify you personally, or determine your e-mail address.
We provide forms and links in places throughout the site for you to send comments, to ask for more information, and to report problems you may experience on our site. Even if you e-mail us through one of our response forms on the site, we cannot determine your e-mail address unless you include it in your response.
Our site contains many links to other sites. Please remember that our privacy policy does not apply to other sites and that we cannot be responsible for their privacy policies, if any.
Please remember that no one can guarantee the complete security of information transmitted over the Internet. Therefore, you should be careful about the personal information which you provide to us or any other site. Rest assured that we will do everything we can to safeguard your information.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or your dealings with this site, please contact us at info@filmmonterey.org.
latest revision January 1st, 2019
Lights, Camera, Economic Action
Monterey County Film Commission would not be possible without these valued local sponsors.
What Can We Help You With?
